{
    "id": "2520617f677a4fb3af8546cf618b6971",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ............................... to Africa recently.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "went",
                "have been",
                "had been"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "138c3bf536704d12baf7f4984f0cda47"
        },
        {
            "question": "I .................................. a letter to him last week.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wrote",
                "have written",
                "write"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1ae1be085d20422d916f4da0d23d0a8b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ............................... him last week.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "saw",
                "have seen",
                "has seen"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6d6df932a2b642049cd551ee4fea1571"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will call you when I .................................. the work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "finish",
                "will finish",
                "would finish"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e5263856f2c946a28681d585ff1957f0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Before he ....................................... to the US, he had finished his studies.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "went",
                "has gone",
                "had gone"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "af331d8bdabf4cce8a896b82100f73b4"
        },
        {
            "question": "He said that he .................................... since morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has been gardening",
                "was gardening",
                "had been gardening"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5aff03434f794b78bbf64efc5a4296f7"
        },
        {
            "question": "The man complained that his mobile phone .....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "had stolen",
                "has stolen",
                "had been stolen"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d034bd36af1d46868c354c51d511b63b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The doctor concluded that the patient ............................... twelve hours of ago.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has been killed",
                "had been killed",
                "was killed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "467ed641418f4a7e8c5604ee41dc805d"
        },
        {
            "question": "By this time next year, he ............................... the construction of his house.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will complete",
                "will have completed",
                "would complete"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f27ce723b4174d029224f85ed5c9fdae"
        },
        {
            "question": "That child ................................... suffering from fever since last week.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "has been",
                "was"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3c14b8b50267415d91be075be3163c4d"
        }
    ]
}